Guide to the John Nolen Papers,1890-1938, 1954-1960.
Nolen, John papers,1890-1938, 1954-1960.
- Series IV. Professional Career
  - Other Professional Activities, and Public Works
    - Public Lectures Illustrated by Slides
      - C344 - Street Widths, American Cities, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C346 - Proposed Residential Street Section, Bridgeport, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C349 - Five Storied Street (Street of the Future), Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C350 - Street Trees, Philadelphia, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C351 - Robert St., Before widening, St. Paul, MN, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C352 - Robert St., After widening, St. Paul, MN, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C353 - Black Acacias, W. 122nd St., Los Angeles, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C354 - Eucalyptus globulus on Scarf St., Los Angeles, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C355 - Eucalyptus globulus, Wilmington, Los Angeles, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C356 - Cocos plumosa, Palms, Private Drive, Santa Barbara, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C357 - Proposed Street Plan, North End, New London, CT, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C358 - Proposed Street Plan, South End, New London, CT, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C359 - Proposed Street Section, New London, CT, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C362 - Streets as Outdoor Art Galleries, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C366 - Overhanging trees between houses, Spring St., Newport, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C367 - Streets New and Old, Newport in contrast, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C368 - Charm of old time street, Newport, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C369 - Beauty of fine trees, Washington St., Newport, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C370 - Washington St. near Chestnut, Newport, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C371 - Picturesque Street, School Sites, Newport, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C372 - Residential Street Scene, Stockbridge, MA, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C374 - Robert St., Before and After Widening, St. Paul, MN, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C376 - Street Views, Garden Cities and Suburbs, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C384 - Airplane View, Place de l'Etoile, Paris, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C386 - Street View, Miami, FL, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C387 - View in Ancon, Canal Zone, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C388 - The Prado, Canal Zone after 7 years, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C389 - Street View, Ancon, C.Z., Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C390 - Old Administration Building, C.Z., Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C391 - Central Ave., St. Petersburg, FL, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C392 - Central Ave., Treatment, St. Petersburg, FL, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C393 - Coconut Palms, Palm Beach, FL, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C394 - Australian Pine, Palm Beach, FL, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C395 - Proposed Street Arcade, Cleveland, Ohio, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C396 - Separating Road Grades, Cleveland, Ohio, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C397 - Profit & Loss in Street Widening, Chaillee Real Estate, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C398 - Street Layout, Syracuse, NY, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C399 - Proposed Street Layout, Syracuse, NY, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C400 - Major Street Plan, San Diego, CA, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C401 - Paseos, Lisbon & Madrid, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C402 - Elevated Street, Chicago, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C403 - Entrance to Broadway, New York City, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C404 - Broadway at Night, New York City, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C405 - Wall Street & Trinity Church, New York City, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C406 - Wacker Drive, Chicago, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C407 - Superhighway, Detroit, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C408 - Cross Sections, Famous American and European Streets, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C409 - Cross Sections, Famous American and European Streets, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C410 - View of Detroit, City of Autos, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C414 - Grade Separation, etc., Superhighway, Wayne County, Detroit, MI, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C415 - Street Congestion, 42nd & Fifth Ave., New York City, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - C423 - Four Bridges over East River, New York, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D10 - City Hall, Cambridge, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D11 - Public Library, Cambridge, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D13 - Town Hall, Brookline, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D14 - Almshouse, Brookline, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D16 - City Hall, Winchester, MA, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D19 - Four Acre School Ground, Oakdale School, East Dedham, MA, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D19 - Oakdale School, 4 Acres, East Dedham, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D20 - School Garden, East Dedham, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D21 - Church, Weston, MA, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D23 - Library(?), Weston, MA, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D26 - City Hall, Worcester, MA, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D27 - New Municipal Building, Springfield, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D29 - Town Square, Plymouth, MA, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D31 - Second Congregational Church, New London, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D37 - "Country Life" Press, D.P. & Co., Garden City, L.I., Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D38 - General Plan, City Avenue School, Montclair, NJ, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D39 - Public School, Glen Ridge, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D42 - Church, Glen Ridge, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D45 - Public Buildings, Proposed grouping, Reading, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D5 - Copley House, Boston, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D55 - Plan for Civic Center, Wilmington, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D56 - Proposed Civic Center, Baltimore, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D58 - Capitol, Washington, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D6 - Bishop Cheverus School, East Boston, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D61 - Terrace Planting, Capitol, Slope, Washington, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D63 - West approach, Exterior Stairways, Capitol, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D64 - View of Capitol from East End of Proposed Mall, Washington, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D68 - Proposed sites for future Public Buildings, Washington, DC, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D69 - Grouping Public Buildings, Roanoke, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D7 - Gardner School, Allstone, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D70 - Grouping Public Buildings, Roanoke, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D72 - Baptist Orphanage, Virginia, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D73 - Baptist Orphanage, Virginia, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D77 - Village Hospital, Biltmore, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D8 - Approach to First Church of Christ, Scientist, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D80 - Group Plan, City of Cleveland, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D81 - Grouping Public Buildings, Cleveland, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D83 - The Court of Honor, World's Fair, Chicago, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D9 - City Hall, Cambridge, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D91 - Plan of Civic Center, Milwaukee, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D97 - Minnesota State Capitol Approaches, St. Paul, MN, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - D99 - Grouping Public Buildings, New Court House, Duluth, MN, Small Box 2 (Box 106)
      - S93 - Plan, Cambridge, MA, 1830; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U17 - Myers Park, Charlotte, NC, 1921; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U18 - Myers Park, Charlotte, NC, 1921; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U4 - Sketch, Town Center, Mariemont, 1922; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
        Glass slide - Broken
      - S100 - Truck Line Highways, NY and environs, 1923; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S99 - Theoretical Diagram, Main Highway Routes, NY and environs, 1923; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U38 - Birds Eye, Airplane View, Mariemont, 1924; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S81 - World Production, Motor Vehicles, 1925; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S95 - Focal Point, Highway Traffic, NY and environs, 1927; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S96 - Area of Interest, Economic Activity, Manhattan, NY Region, 1927; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S97 - Minimum Weekend Highway Congestion, 1927; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S103 - Trend Types of Dwellings, Los Angeles, 1928; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T35 - Proportion Business Zone & Population, Los Angeles Region, Chart, 1928; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U100 - Key Plan, Radburn, New York Region, 1928; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U113 - Church & School, Mariemont, 1928; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T40 - Zoning & Building Heights, Governed by Street Widths, 1929; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T41 - Volumetric Zoning, Boston & St. Louis, 1929; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T42 - Zoning Cartoon, 1929; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S101 - Normal Midday Traffic, Fifth Ave., NY, 1930; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S102 - Population Chart, Greater London, 1930; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S104 - Planning Municipal Development, Chart, U.S.C. of C, 1930; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S109 - Aerial Map, Princeton, NJ, 1930; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S94 - Airplane View, Manhattan, 1930; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T39 - Rogers Buildings, Santa Barbara, 1930; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U114 - Sidewalk underpass, Radburn, NJ, 1930; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S92 - Map of Boston, 1630 - 1930; Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S105 - Newport News & Peninsula, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S106 - Port Facilities, Newport News, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S107 - Mosaic Aerial, Newport News, VA, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S108 - U.S.G.S. Map, Wolfeboro, NY, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S82 - Deaths due to Motor Vehicles, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S83 - Traffic Progress in Cities, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S84 - Traffic Relief Loop, Boston, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S85 - Motor Vehicle Registration, Chicago, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S86 - Growth in Motor Vehicle Production, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S87 - Chart Auto, Death Rate, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S88 - Fruit Production, Florida, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S89 - Airplane Survey, Tamiami, FL, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - S98 - Diagram, NY Region, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T10 - Comparison, With or Without Zone Plan, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T11 - Store on Residential Street, Milwaukee, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T12 - Public Garage Among Apartments, Milwaukee, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T13 - Factory on Residential Street, Milwaukee, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T14 - Stables erected in Residential District, St. Louis, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T15 - First Tenement in Block of Single Family Homes, St. Louis, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T16 - Undesirable Store in Residential District, St. Louis, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T20 - High Buildings, Johnstown, PA, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T21 - Airplane View, Birmingham, AL, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T22 - Building line problem, Brookline, MA, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T23 - Front Yards, Paterson, NJ, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T24 - Rear Yards, Paterson, NJ, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T28 - Junk Warehouse, etc., Detroit, MI, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T29 - Apartment House in Residential Section, Detroit, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T30 - Heights & Area District, Manhattan, NY, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T31 - What Zoning Means, Cartoon, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T32 - Horizontal Zoning, Cartoon, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T34 - Future Skyscraper, Cartoon, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T36 - Retail Business Frontage Requirements, Chicago, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T37 - Zoning Facts, Los Angeles, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T38 - New Architecture, County Hospital, Los Angeles, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - T43 - Zone Plan, Wyomissing, PA, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U104 - Perspective View, Superblock, Radburn, NJ, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U105 - Preliminary Town Plan, Radburn, NY, 1928, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U106 - Radburn Superblock, Radburn, NJ, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U108 - Shopping Center, Apartments & Houses, NY 1930, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U14 - Proposed Hospital Group, Mariemont, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U15 - Pensioners Cottages, Mariemont, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U16 - Sketch, Farm Buildings, Mariemont, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U19 - Myers Park, Charlotte, NC, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U20 - Overlook Colony, Claymont, DE, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U27 - Satellite Towns around London, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U33 - Dogwood Park, Mariemont, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U34 - Wooster Pike, Mariemont, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U35 - Valuation Group, Mariemont, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U36 - Scheme for Architectural Groups, Mariemont, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U37 - Scheme, Material Group, Mariemont, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U39 - Approach to Works, Kistler, PA, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U40 - Small Houses, Kistler, PA, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U41 - Gardens, Kistler, PA, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U42 - Community Building, Kistler, PA, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U43 - Homes & Gardens, Kistler, PA, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U44 - Factory & Village, Mount Union Refractories Company, Kistler, PA, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U48 - Street Sections, Bellair, FL, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U49 - Sketch, Bellair, FL, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U50 - Plan, Rex Beach Property, Bellair, FL, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U53 - Types of Architecture, Palos Verdes, CA, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U57 - Regional Study, Venice & Nokomis, FL, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U6 - Key Map (whole city), Mariemont, Cincinnati, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U7 - Key Map (eastern section), Mariemont, Cincinnati, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U73 - Theory Satellite Towns, Whitten, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U74 - Town Planning Scheme, Unwin, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U75 - Diagram, New Town with Suburbs & Satellites, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U76 - Venetian Canal, Proposed, Coral Gables, Miami, FL, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U78 - Key Map, Tamiami, FL, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U79 - Regional Plan, Tamiami, FL, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U8 - Existing Conditions, Mariemont, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U82 - Malago Cove Plaza, Palos Verdes, CA, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U83 - Public School, Palos Verdes, FL, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U94 - Street Plan, Mariemont and Western, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U95 - Airplane View, Mariemont, OH, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U96 - Organization Chart, Mariemont, OH, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U97 - Organization Chart, Mariemont, OH, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U98 - General Plan, Grovemont & Asheville, NC, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - U99 - Neighborhood Centre, Whitten's Scheme, Small Box 3 (Box 106)
      - National Conference in City Planning Plan, Bourne, Camey, Nolen, Haldeman, 1 (Box 108)
      - General Plan of Franklin Park, Boston, MA, 1885; 2 (Box 108)
        Glass slide, Broken
      - Buenos Aires, Paseo de Julie (Place of July), 3 (Box 108)
      - Charlotte Township, Charlotte, NC, 4 (Box 108)
      - Jack, Sketch by Mr. Day, 5 (Box 108)
      - Fa Plato, Argentine Rep., Fa Municipalidad (City Hall), 6 (Box 108)
      - Fa Plato, Argentine Rep., Palaes de Governamiente, 7 (Box 108)
      - Naples dal Nomero (Bay of Naples), Naples, 8 (Box 108)
      - Paris, Plan of Champes Elysees, 9 (Box 108)
      - Reading, PA, 1748; 10 (Box 108)
      - Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, Part of Waterfront, The Suburb of Botogogo, 11 (Box 108)
      - Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, Public Gardens, 12 (Box 108)
      - Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, Recently opened street, 13 (Box 108)
      - Sao Paulo, Brazil, Avenue Feiodente, 14 (Box 108)
      - Sao Paulo, Brazil, Central R.R. Station, 15 (Box 108)
      - Sao Paulo, Brazil, Governors Palace at left, Dept. of Agriculture in Center, 16 (Box 108)
      - Sao Paulo, Brazil, Public Garden, 17 (Box 108)
      - Santa Barbara, CA, Station, 18 (Box 108)
      - Williamsburg, VA, Plan of City, 19 (Box 108)
      - Kistler, PA, Single family houses, 20 (Box 108)
      - Kistler, PA, Single family houses, 21 (Box 108)
      - Kistler, PA, General view showing 2 family house, 22 (Box 108)
      - Kistler, PA, Single family house, 23 (Box 108)
      - Kistler, PA, General view, 24 (Box 108)
      - Cleveland Cliffs Iron Co. Employee's house (North Lake location), July 15, 1916; 25 (Box 108)
      - Delaware and Lackawana Rail and Coal Co., Nautiealse, PA; House and plan, Forest Hills Gardens, Long Island, NY, 26 (Box 108)
      - Forest Hills Gardens, Long Island, NY, General View of Group III, 27 (Box 108)
      - The Norton Co., Worcester, MA; Indian Hill, Plan, 28 (Box 108)
      - Norton Grinding Co., Worcester, MA, Semi,detached dwelling and single family dwelling, 29 (Box 108)
      - Derby, CT, Osborne Cottage #2, 30 (Box 108)
      - Derby, CT, Osborne Cottage #4, 31 (Box 108)
      - Derby, CT, Wailsingmen's Cottage #3, 32 (Box 108)
      - Kenosha Homes Company, Parkview, 33 (Box 108)
      - Firestone Park, House A, Alsren Ohio, 34 (Box 108)
      - Concrete House, Detail, Forest Hills Gardens, Long Island, NY, 35 (Box 108)
      - Studies in Economic Construction Progress Record, 36 (Box 108)
      - Chart showing speed of erection, 37 (Box 109)
      - Savannah Park & Tree Commission - Map of City, 36-1 (Box 109)
        Glass slide - Corner broken
      - Savannah Park & Tree Commission - Bird's Eye View of Daffin Park, 36-2 (Box 109)
      - Savannah Park & Tree Commission - Daffin Park, General Plan, 36-3 (Box 109)
      - Westover Heights Co. (Lynchburg, VA) - General Plan for Westover Heights, 37-1 (Box 109)
      - Westover Heights Co. (Lynchburg, VA) - General Plan, 37-2 (Box 109)
        Glass slide - Not in print books
      - Roanoke Civic Improvement Committee - City Plan, General Plan for the Remodeling of Roanoke, 51-1 (Box 109)
      - Roanoke Civic Improvement Committee - City Plan, Grouping of public buildings in connection with the remodeling of Roanoke, 51-2 (Box 109)
      - San Diego Civic Improvement Committee - City Plan, Government Top, 52-1 (Box 109)
        Glass slide - Not in print book
      - San Diego Civic Improvement Committee - City Plan, Municipal Group, 52-3 (Box 109)
      - San Diego Civic Improvement Committee - City Plan, The Bay Front (Wash Drawing), 52-3 (Box 109)
      - Bristol, CT - The Price and Lee Co.'s 1918 Directory City Map with additions made by F.J.M. for use of John Nolen, 1918; Misc. 38 (Box 109)
      - Tyrone, NM - Perspective and Plan of Town Center from Area Forum, April 1918; Misc. 39 (Box 109)
      - Burlington, VT - Small spaces between houses from Udetta D. Brown's Burlington Housing Report (Hous 90), Misc. 40 (Box 109)
      - Burlington, VT - A one-family house (contrast with Misc. 40 from Udetta D. Brown Burlington Housing Report (Hous 90)), Misc. 41 (Box 109)
        Glass slide - 2 479
      - Map of Greenfield, MA, Misc. 42 (Box 109)
        Glass slide - Slide negative
      - Denver Union Station, Misc. 43 (Box 109)
        Glass slide - A66
      - Albany Station, Misc. 44 (Box 109)
      - Lincoln Park Refectory - Chicago, IL, Misc. 45 (Box 109)
      - Philadelphia Bridges (from Art Jury Report), Misc. 46 (Box 109)
      - Philadelphia Bridges (from Art Jury Report), Misc. 47 (Box 109)
      - Union Park Gardens - Wilmington, DE - Street Scene, Fall 1919; Misc. 48 (Box 109)
      - Providence, RI - Visitors first view of Providence), Misc. 49 (Box 109)
      - Providence, RI - Union Station, Frontspiece: a modern city eg Kink, 1909; Misc. 50 (Box 109)
      - City Hall - Bordeaux, France; Street View & Civic Center - Bordeaux, France, Misc. 51 (Box 109)
        Glass slide - D302; D301
      - City Hall - Bordeaux, France; Bridge (Le Port et la Fleche St Michel - Bordeaux, France), Misc. 52 (Box 109)
        Glass slide - D302; B239
      - Block & Lot Problems - Water at park frontage - See L.A. April 1911 (Pope), Misc. 52 (Box 109)
        Glass slide - K84
      - Promenade at Monti Carlo; Potsdamer Platz, Misc. 53 (Box 109)
        Glass slide - B238, C382
      - Airplane View - Trafalgar Square London, Misc. 55 (Box 109)
        Glass slide - D300
      - Glen Ridge & Citizen's Committee - General Plan, Glen Ridge Inn (Perspective), 62 1/2 - 2 (Box 110)
      - La Crosse Park Commission - City Park System, Topo map, 62-1.1 (Box 110)
        Glass slide - Clearest, Not in print book
      - La Crosse Park Commission - City Park System, Topo map, 62-1.2 (Box 110)
      - La Crosse Park Commission - City Park System, Levee Park, 62-2 (Box 110)
      - La Crosse, WI - City Park System, 62-3 (Box 110)
      - Smith's Agricultural Show - General Plan, Construction Plan, 65-2 (Box 110)
      - Smith's Agricultural School - General Plan, Perspective, 65-3 (Box 110)
      - Glen Ridge & Citizen's Committee - General Plan, Suggestive Plan for Glen Ridge Inn, 67 1/2 - 1 (Box 110)
      - Montclair Art Commission - General Plan, Plan for the Improvement of Montclair-Glenridge, 67-1 (Box 110)
      - Montclair Art Commission - General Plan, Montclair Town Center, 67-2 (Box 110)
      - Montclair Art Commission - General Plan, Bloomfield Ave., 67-3 (Box 110)
      - Montclair Art Commission - General Plan, Proposed Business Corner, 67-4 (Box 110)
      - Map of Boston, MA, 1722; Misc. 56 (Box 110)
        Glass slide - 557
      - Survey of Flint Diagrams - Growth of population, Growth of factory payrole, Misc. 57 (Box 110)
        Glass slide - 552
      - Kansas City - Pavilion in Park, Misc. 58 (Box 110)
      - Denver - Civic Center (Sketch), Misc. 59 (Box 110)
      - Niagara Falls, NY - City Hall in a grouping of public buildings (Sketch), Misc. 60 (Box 110)
      - Colonnade & Post Office - Chautauqna, NY, Misc. 61 (Box 110)
        Glass slide - D297
      - Village Green & PO, Chautauqna, NY; Typical Street View, Chautauqna, NY (Slide of 296), Misc. 62 (Box 110)
        Glass slide - D296; C381
      - Chautauqna, NY - "Zoning Chautauqna", Misc. 63 (Box 110)
      - Bristol, CT in 1776 (Map), 1776; Misc. 64 (Box 110)
      - Bristol, CT - U.S. Geol. Survey Topo., Misc. 65 (Box 110)
      - Toronto, Canada - Recreation, dredges at work, Industrial District; Frontpiece, Annual Report Toronto Harbor Commissioners, 1912; Misc. 66 (Box 110)
      - Bar Harbor, Map of, 1907; Misc. 67 (Box 110)
      - Bar Harbor, Map, Misc. 68 (Box 110)
      - Bar Harbor, Map of Mt. Desert Island, Misc. 69 (Box 110)
      - Gardner, MA - Street Scene; War Monument, Misc. 70 (Box 110)
        Glass slide - 2482, 2484
      - Gardner, MA - Old Town Hall, Misc. 71 (Box 110)
        Glass slide - 2483
      - Gardner, MA - U.S. Geological Survey Topo, Misc. 72 (Box 110)
        Glass slide - 2482
      - Gardner, MA - City Map, Misc. 73 (Box 110)
        Glass slide - 2481 - Broken
      - Reading Civic Association City Plan - Suggestion for Grouping of Public Buildings, 77-1 (Box 111)
      - Madison Citizen's Committee - City Plan, Topographical Chain of 5 Lakes, 80-1 (Box 111)
      - Madison Citizen's Committee - City Plan, Sketch of proposed State St. Triangle (Clearest), 80-4.1 (Box 111)
      - Madison Citizen's Committee - City Plan, Sketch of proposed State St. Triangle, 80-4.2 (Box 111)
      - Madison Citizen's Committee - City Plan, State St. Approach to Capitol, as it is, wires removed (Sketch), 80-5 (Box 111)
      - Madison Citizen's Committee - City Plan, State St. Approach to Capitol, Proposed (Sketch), 80-6 (Box 111)
      - Round Top Land Company, Land Subdivision - General Plan, 83-1.1 (Box 111)
        Glass slide - Clearer
      - Round Top Land Company, Land Subdivision - General Plan, 83-1.2 (Box 111)
      - Round Top Land Company, Land Subdivision - Plan (Bird's Eye), 83-2 (Box 111)
        Glass slide - Small size